Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
- Series X. Labor Management Programs
  - Interdepartmental fruit committee, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - California trip, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - New York State Horticultural Society annual meeting - Kay Embrey presentation, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Labor law changes workshop, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Evictions from labor camps (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Discipline and discharge Of employees workshop, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Harvest Labor management for quality fruit panel, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Federal and state labor laws presentation - Horticultural Society, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Farm labor laws panel, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Farm labor laws panel, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) presentation at fruit schools, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Harvest Management Article - Embrey (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Improving Supervision presentation on Long Island, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Don Rogers - Management consultant, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Fruit mailing list, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Dairy group presentations, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - New York State minimum wage order for farmworkers, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - In depth management for vegetable storage, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Training employees presentation - Vegetable conference, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Retaining farm labor presentation on Long Island, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Agricultural agent survey concerning labor management, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - DeMay labor, 1987-1990 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Million dollar management, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Field sanitation presentation, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Management of supervisors presentation in Hudson Valley, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Front line supervisors presentation (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Human resource management on the farm - Letter series, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Labor rules and regulations at empire farm managers, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Small farm labor regulations - Presentation at vegetable conference in Albany, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Spanish classes (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) workshop presentation - Embrey, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Immigration law - Oswego, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - SAW-RAW - Embrey, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Employer sanctions - Information for employers (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) Cornell Cooperative Extension news article, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Improving personal management presentation in West Virginia, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Labor laws presentation in Albany, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Middle manager's perspective presentation for empire farm managers, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Labor regulations presentation in Albany by producers, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Minimum wage Resource materials (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Your legal rights as an employee (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Outline of selected programs, 1981-1990 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Pro-Dairy, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Agriculture employers fair and workshop - DeNarree, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Mexican dairy workers, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Costa Rica connection, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension human resources pilot project (not funded), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Agriculture production week presentation, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Culturally diverse labor force presentation in Albany, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - International workers in New York State survey, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Hiring of aliens - Oswego County and Chautauqua County, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Minimum wage with Maloney (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Minimum wage calculation, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Laws Related to Employment of Migrant Farmworkers - Embrey, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Grafting, budding, and pruning workshop, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Some background information on New York and Pam Apple industry - Holt and North, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Foucs on farmworkers series - Embrey, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Farm minimum wage law changes - Overheads, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Human resources pilot project, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Employee training program - Agriculture markets, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Food and agriculture network, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Hispanics on dairy farms in various counties, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 80)
- Series XI. Agricultural Careers Development Project
  - Agriculture upgrade training in California, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Proposal support letters, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Grant proposal, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Grant proposal - Cornell portion, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cornell project piece (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Position description - Rural Opportunities Inc. project manager (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Rural Opportunities Inc. grant application, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Rural Opportunities Inc. grant application, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Grant application - Cornell portion, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Monthly reports, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - ACDP - progress and final reports (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Executive Summary - RNYFO (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - ACDP presentation New York Dept. of Labor rural employment annual conference (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Project summary - Embrey (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Closing of project, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Jim Holt correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Farm Journal articles, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Newsletter articles (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Photos (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Meeting minutes - Advisory board, Rural Opportunities Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Programs (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Series in Wayne County and Orleans - Course records (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Programs, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Topics (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Basic fruit production - Course notebook (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Basic fruit production - Course notebook (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Basic fruit school, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Fruit Course evaluations (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Interview with employers concerning management, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Supervising employees course, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Managing and motivating employees course, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Managing and motivating employees course, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Management services, 1984-02-1984-03 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Farm labor contractors meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Fruit harvest quality control course, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Presentation for owners, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Series XII. Labor Management - Cornell
  - Training Employees for Farmwork - Bradt, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Incentive Pay Plans Packing Houses - Blakely Spencer, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Management and cost control in producing apples for fresh market, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Viable farmer - Worker relationship - Adams, How and Larson, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - An Economic Study of Regular Hired Labor - Cunningham, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Workers in Agribusiness - Cornell publication, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Capital and Labor Requirement for Farming - Casler, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Mechanization and the Migrant in New York State - Taylor Geneseo, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Human Relations on the Farm Curriculum - Frank, Spalding and How, 1970-1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Retirement Plans, Housing and Fringe Benefits for New York Career Farmworkers - Bratton, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Agriculture Technology and the Migrant Farm Laborer - Levine, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cost of Seasonal Agricultural Employment - Bauder, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Improving the labor Management on Dairy Farms - Kohl, Bratton, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Characteristics of New York Career Farmworkers - Beech and Bratton, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Apple Harvest Labor Productivity in Chaplain Valley 1970-1975 - Fisher, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Labor Management Practices on Selected New York Dairy Farms - Kohl, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Labor Management Study on Selected Monroe County Farms, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Labor Productivity of Apple Harvest Workers - Fisher, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Workers - A Question of Property Rights - Fisher, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Farm Labor in New York - Statistical Overveiw - Fisher, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Program in agriculture proposal - Niagara County, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - County farm training programs, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Farm training - Orleans County (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Farm employee training - Geneseo County, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Supervision of seasonal employees proposal - Wayne, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Study of Labor Management Practices on New York State Dairy Farms, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Personnel Management on Dairy Farms - How and Bratton, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Incentive Plans for Use on Dairy Farms - Bratton, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Farm labor management - Home study course, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - 30 Farm Labor Management - Home study course for fruit and vegetable growers, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Managing Seasonal Hired Labor - Course by Bratton and How, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Managing Seasonal Hired Labor - Course by Bratton and How, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Manpower Programs in Extension - Fisher, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Human Resources Management Workshop - How and Bratton, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Human resource workshop, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Labor Management Practices on New York Dairy Farms - Bratton and Kwiatowski, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Harvest forms - Wolanyk (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Fruit farm cost studies, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Migrant Farmworkers Earnings: A Human Capital Approach - White-Means, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Employee Management Seminar - Rogers, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Employee Management Seminar - Rogers, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Employee recruitment and selection workshop, Onondaga County, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Outlook for Agriculture Labor for 1989 and Beyond - Miller New York Horticulture Society (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Managing farm personnel - In-service workshop, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Papers by Robert Milligan, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Farm Labor in the 90's - curriculum by Milligan, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Managing Farm Labor in the 90's - curriculum by Milligan, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Recruitment and selection of farm employees - Workshop curriculum, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Recruitment and selection of farm employees - Workshop curriculum, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Pro dairy management curriculum - Day 1 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Pro dairy management curriculum - Day 1 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - The Manager: Pro Dairy Newsletter, 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Wages and Benefits of Full Time Non-Family Employees - Maloney, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Dairy Farm Worker Training at TLCC - Maloney, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Writing an Employee Handbook - Maloney, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Survey of Recruitment and Selection Practices - Florist crops - Maloney, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Produce New York pilot workshop, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Produce New York pilot workshop, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - New York State Horticultural Society annual meeting, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - New York State Horticultural Society annual meeting, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Bibliography of horticulture product marketing and related topic papers - Fiqueroa, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Agricultural Resolve, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Series XIII. Labor Management-National and State
  - Recruiting, training and developing workers for coops - USDA, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural employment work group, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture Labor in the 1980's: Survey with recommendations agricultural employment work group (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural employment work group - Connecticut meeting, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural employment work group and Cornell, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Agricultural employment work group and extension - Nationally, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Meeting training and upgrading needs in American agricultural employment work group, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural careers institute proposal, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Personnel management handbook - Manpower programs in extension, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Personnel management handbook, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Personnel management handbook, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Personnel management resource file: Manpower programs in extension (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Personnel management resource file: Manpower programs in extension (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - National Council of Agricultural Employers newsletters, 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - National Council of Agricultural Employers newsletters, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Natioinal Council of Agricultural Employers newsletters, 1991-1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - National Council of Agricultural Employers annual meeting, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Farm Personnel Management - Thomas and Erven, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Managing farm personnel in-service - Northeast extension, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Management of Migrant Labor in Pennsylvania Apple Harvest - Holt Study, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Agricultural labor management development - Dickinson Law School, Pennsylvania, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Agricultural labor management development - Dickinson Law School, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Effective personnel management in orchard - Presentation in Dickinson Law School, Pennsylvania, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Agricultural labor management development - Dickinson Law School, participant notebook, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Agricultural labor management development - Dickinson Law School, participant notebook, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Agricultural Employment - P. Roth of Pennsylvania, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Human Relations on Michigan Fruit and Vegetable Farms - Voland, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Personnel Management on the Farm - Speicher, et al, Michigan, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Michigan - Al Shaply (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Farm Employers Handbook - Shapley, Michigan, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Migrant and seasonal workers in Michigan, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Incentive Wage System for Harvesting Oranges - Fox, Arizona, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Personnel Training and Management Guide - McAllister, Delaware, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Labor management - Florida (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Training for farmworkers - Florida, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Florida Cooperative Extension (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Iowa programs (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Extension publications - Kentucky, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Extension publications - Massachusetts (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Agricultural careers project - North Carolina, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Increasing importance of labor management on large dairy farms - Ervin, Ohio, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Role and responsibility of Texas Department of Agriculture in developing agricultural labor policy and programs - Glover, Texas, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Migrant labor law - Virginia, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - 1992 apple harvest in West Virginia, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Labor Productivity in Apple Picking-Washington, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Use of labor in Pacific Northwest agriculture production, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Wisconsin programs, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Agricultural Training Institute - Ontario, Canada, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Working with people - Agricultural Training Institute -Canada (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Reports by Kenneth McEwan, Ontario, Canada, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - British Columbia, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Harvesting Cost in Eastern United Sates - Holden, Ontario, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Series XIV. Farms Labor Laws Regulations
  - Farmworker rights handbooks - Rural Opportunities Inc., 1975, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Farmworker rights handbooks - Legal services (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Farmworker rights handbooks - Department of Labor, 1975-1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Impact of Extending UIB to Agricultural Workers in New York State - Bauder, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Considerations in Extending UIB to Agricultural Workers in New York State - Bauder, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Legal services - Fisher, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Telephones in camps, 1979, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Survey of farm labor related needs of Cooperative Extension agents Babcock and Embrey, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Fruit Notes newsletter, 1981-1997 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Migrant Seasonal Agricultural Protection Act (Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Worker Protection Act) regs forms, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Worker Protection Act - Workers rights (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Transportation Glassboro Case - Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Worker Protection Act, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Social security and farmworkers, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - New York State minimum wage order, 1982, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Minimum wage order changes S. Mitchell correspondence, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - New York State minimum wage order, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Changes in New York State Farm Minimum Wage Law - Maloney and Embrey, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - New York State minimum wage law change - New York State, Federal, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - New York State Department of Labor summary of New York State labor laws, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Farm work agreements, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - New York State Department of Labor division of labor standards, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Farm management news articles - How and Bratton (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Extension labor newsletters (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - College of Agriculture and Life Sciences farm labor regional meeting, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - New York State farm labor laws, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Field sanitation OSHA notes and regulations, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Field sanitation proposed regulations, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Field sanitation education project - Rural Opportunities Inc., 1987 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Federal field sanitation resources, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Field sanitation state, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - New York State minimum wage order for farmworkers, 1985, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - New York State Department of Labor guidelines for investigators, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Summary of New York State laws relating to farm and FP employment - Department of Labor, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Farm labor guidelines - Lehman, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Farm regulations correspondence - Embrey, 1985-1989 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Farm labor contractors registration - State and federal (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Federal minimum wage law (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Child labor laws agriculture (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Farm workers and Fair Labor Standards Act, 1977, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Unemployment insurance Department of Labor (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Workers compensation (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - New York State pesticide bill, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - H-2A temporary workers in agriculture - United States Department of Labor, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Posting requirements - Demarree (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Agriculture affiliates posting poster, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Agriculture employers meeting - Wayne County, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Immigration employment verification, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Rights responsibilities and regulations workshop by Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Exclusion of farmworkers from New York labor laws summary, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Rights of women farmworkers - United States Department of Labor, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Farm labor regulations - Fisher, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Cornell's farm labor regulations - Grossman, 1987, 1989, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Agriculture employment law summary - Grossman (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Farmworker protective laws, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Federal laws and regulations, 1989, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Agriculture Recruitment System Employers Guide - United States Department of Labor, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Rights, responsibilities and regulations - Agriculture affiliates, 1992, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Disability insurance - DeMarree, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Series XV. Government Bodies and Groups
  - New York State Department of Labor - Number of workers, 1957-1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - New York State Department of Labor - Number of workers, 1982-1985, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Employment bulletin - Department of Labor, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Agricultural Employment bulletin - Department of Labor, 1991-1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Estimated peak population Of interstate workers in New York by ethnic group, arrival and departure dates, crops, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Hired Farm Working Force of 1971, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Social and economic characteristics of Spanish origin farmworkers in 1973, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Where Have All the Farmworkers Gone? Statistical annihilation of migrant farmworkers by federal agencies, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - People on the Farm - United States Department of Agriculture, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - The Hired Farm Working Force of 1977, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Hired Farmworkers Background and Trend for the 80's, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Hired Farm Working Force of 1981, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Counting Hired Farmworkers - Points to Consider - Whitener, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Population and Labor Force of 1990-2050, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - An Analysis of Data Sources and Methodologies for Enumerating Migrant Farmworkers - New York State - Hinrichs, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Hired Farm Labor Use on Fruit Vegetable and Horticultural Speciality Farms, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Farm Labor National Agricultural Statistics Service, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Farm and Farm-Related Employment in the 90's - United States Department of Agriculture, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Profile of Hired Farmworkers, 1994 Annual Averages, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - New York State Hispanic Population: Description and Evaluation Of Mexican Descent Group - Figueroa, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Research and extension publication on agricultural labor, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Bibliographies on migrant farmworkers, 1978, 1978, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Lewis Report to Government's Committee on Migrants and Rural Poor, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Inter-agency Coordinating Committee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Farmworker Bill of Rights Act - Chisholm - HR4453, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Minimum Wage for Farmworkers - A412 - Eve, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - New York State Advisory Council on Minimum Wage Standards for Farmworkers, 1985-1994 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Directory of service agencies represented on ICC, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - New York Agriculture 2000, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Agriculture 2000 conference and correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Legal Service Corporation, 1987, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Liberalism to the Test: African American Migrant Farmworkers and New York State, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 32)